# **Jake Knowles**

Front End Developer Born 1994 in London



#### About me

Enthusiastic and creative Front-end web developer with over 5 years of experience. I am knowledgeable in a range of Front-end languages and tools to build and maintain a wide range of web applications. I am a dependable team player and keen learner who thrives when faced with learning new tools which enhance my professional skillset.

#### Skills



# Contact





07947108062

iknowles94



#### Experience

## Front-End Developer

**IPUSHPULL** 

since April 2019

Migrated the main web app from AngularJS to Vue and build a reusable component architecture to use throughout other intergrations such as Symphony and Microsoft Teams. Implement a continuous integration while running tests using Cypress and Bitbucket Pipelines.

### Front-End Developer

Amigo Partnership

August 2015 - April 2019

I was working in a small development team of 6 to create and develop a bespoke CMS using AngularJS and our own API using GraphQL/Rails. I am responsible for leading a team to deliver a bespoke CMS and web app (including a native app, using Cordova), on a range of clients, such as, Rolls-Royce, O2 and Xcina. I am assisting with the growth of the company, to help improve the workflow and production throughout the development team in order to work more efficiently.

## Junior Front-End and Email Developer

Mccormack & Morrison

October 2013 - July 2015

Building and maintaining websites and landing pages for companies using wordpress. Creating responsive emails and newsletters that work over multiple platforms.

#### Web Developer Apprentice

Contentive

September 2012 - October 2013

Building, testing and maintaining business standard websites for clients including Landing pages and HTML Email Templates.



### Education

IT Professional (Web Development) August 2012 - August 2013 Level 3 Diploma

ICT- BTEC National, History, Media Studies September 2010 - May 2012 A Level

# Projects

#### **Centurions Major Golf App**

React & Node

An ongoing project which tracks events from golf tournaments with stats and a leaderboard. It is built using the latest version of React using hooks.